2lipslive.com 2013-07-24

# 2LIPSLIVE.com

| Privacy Policy  
---  
  
In order to provide this service, This website must collect, use, and share certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, who we share it with, and how you can contact customer service in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect, use, and share. The information this website collects from you helps us better serve you and the online community by continually updating this site with new features. The data that this website collects and maintains is as follows:

**Information that you provide to us:**   
This website receives and stores all information that you enter on our sign-up (join), buy credit pages or any other page that ask for information either from us or our partner billing companies, except credit card numbers, this will be only collected by our partner companies who do the billing for this website. This includes: 

  * Everything on every payment pages - your e-mail address, credit card number (only by the companies who do the billing), expiration date, first name, last name, address, city, state, zip, country, and your agreement to be bound by this website, Epoch, CCbill, Verotel terms and conditions.

**Information that we automatically receive and store:**   
This website receives and stores certain information whenever you download web pages, or send us e-mail or forms. For example: 

  * We identify the numerical IP address assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider.
  * E-mail Correspondence, this website often requests a confirmation when you receive and open an e-mail communication delivered by this website. We archive all e-mail sent in and out of our network, and we identify the origination IP address of all e-mail sent into our network.
  * We keep track of many things more for use in court of law if there might be fraud.

**Information from third parties:**   
From time to time, this website requests and receives information from third parties and compares it to the information that you have provided. The main purpose for this is loss prevention. 

**Protection of your privacy:**   
This website will release data when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law and enforce our Agreement. We will under no other circumstances release any information other then this reason or for use against fraud, we will hand over all information to the right instancies. We work together with instancies who will investigate the fraud into the fullest and eventually make work of it. 

It is your obligation to provide this website with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide us with such information could void any Agreement between you and this website. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your purchase request, responding to customer service inquiries, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, customer service and fulfill obligations to you. This website's employees have access to your information on a need-to-know basis. This website will Not sell your information to a third party for any reason. 

In addition, to our billing companies, as part of the credit card processing system must provide limited information to the services that connect it to the companies that perform the banking functions. The credit card associations have strict privacy rules that these companies must adhere to in order to be authorized to receive and process credit card transactions. Our billing companies will never knowingly provide your information outside of this system.

Our billing companies employs the latest and best techniques available for protecting its systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and is constantly upgrading its security as better methods become available. All information is stored behind firewalls and other sophisticated security systems. There data center utilizes state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the facility.

This Privacy Policy was posted in February 2001. This site reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. This website takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. We will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates.

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the information this website has stored about you should be send to the customer service from the website.  

Terms Of Service  
---  
  
You must read and agree to these Terms of Service before joining this website. By signing up you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice. You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at: http://www.2lipslive.com/info.php#terms

This website provides users with access to adult material. Therefor you certify that your atleast 18 years of age. If you provide any information that is not true, accurate or current, your account can be deleted. You also agree that you choose to receive the Service and that we in no way are sending you this Service. You agree and understand that we are in no way responsible for any concequences of using the Service.

This website also sends out emails to its customers, about Service updates and reminders. You agree that we can send you this information. You can always opt-out of receiving emails from us or by letting us know to write to customer service or change your settings in your account or use the unsubcribe link.

Your account login details may not be shared, given or sold to others. Your login details are yours and can only be used by you. You understand that it might also be that access from certain countries is denied and therefor access to the service will not be possible. You are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your account. You can have only One(1) account. If you like multiple account, let us know and we can create one extra manually, with our permission.

As This website is an interactive site, you understand that you have to respect other customers using the Service and that you can not impersonate any person or entity. You can also not gather or take any kind of information from the employees or customers on the site (that includes taking screenshots). The service is only for own enjoyment and can not be used to promote other websites or products.

Sales made are final. If you were unsatisfied about the service you got, Please contact us. As we can reupdate your virtual account with this website (virtual e-wallet account is build in to our Service for each customer, which gives us the ease to serve you for these kind of issues, refunds are therefor not necessary).

This website can change prices on the site without notice. That means the price per minute for a private show or the subscription to the gold area. Any credits or subscriptions purchased before the price change can not and will not be refunded. Also credit purchases for private shows are not bound to any model or price. They simply update only your virtual account at this website.

It is not allowed to exchange contact information in anyway possible with models or other customers from This website. This includes not by chat, visual, email, instant messengers, messaging systems, phone, etc. Including promoting of other websites or services is not allowed. If found so your account will be closed.

You agree to indemnify and hold this website and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, employees, partners, broadcasters and licensors harmless from any claim or demand. In no way we can be held responsible for any cause. This website reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify temporarily or permanently the Service without notice. As well as to cancel, disable or delete any accounts without notice.

For any concern about the information we hold about you. Please read our Privacy Policy: http://www.2lipslive.com/info.php#privacy

Questions regarding the Terms of Service should be send to the customer service from the website.  

18 U.S.C. 2257  
---  
  
"In compliance with the Federal Labeling and Record-Keeping Law (also known as 18 U.S.C. 2257), all models located within our domain were 18 years of age or older during the time of photography. All models proof of age is held by the custodian of records, which is listed below, organized by producer. All content and images are in full compliance with the requirements of 18 U.S.C. 2257 and associated regulations."

**Custodian of kept records required by 18 U.S.C. 2257:**

Custodian record keeper  
Itm LLC  
Jindrisska, 110 00  
Europe   

Studios & Models  
---  
Join 2LipsLive.com and broadcast your live webcam. 

  * If you are a **Studio Owner** and you are interested in cooperating with this website: [Signup here](http://studios.2lipslive.com/signup.php).
  * If you are a **Model** and you are interested in cooperating with this website: [Signup here](http://models.2lipslive.com/signup.php).

Webmasters and Affiliates  
---  
Webmaster add live webcams to your sites. Completely for free and earn high % on the sales. 

  * High commission payouts. Especially for quality or large volumes of traffic.
  * White label / co-brand the whole webcam site.
  * Free hosted galleries. Can be branded in your name.
  * Live model iframe tools.
  * FLV flash movies.
  * IM popup ads.
  * XML feeds.
  * High converting banners.
  * Webmaster referral payouts.
  * Need custom solutions...let us know.

visit our webmaster affiliate site at: <http://www.2lipscash.com/>
